let's go
hi Julia hello
hello hi
nice to meet you I'm the Major Hong Min Young
you can just call me Rachel
Perfect and hi everyone how are you
to Danza hi
thank you thank you
we're so excited to be here OK please have us sit here
so Julia are you ready for a consultation
I'm ready okay haha
let's have a tea
so how are you hi
hi how are you doing
I'm doing good how are you
I'm doing great thank you
I can see your skin is totally fine
so yeah yeah
oh yeah
you already know yeah
that is great you know
I love the attitude yeah
so do you have any certain look that you want to go for today
or maybe something like
more I like natural looking makeup
but just like really accentuate what I have okay
um well
I'm going on a date after this
so I just wanna look like the best I could possibly look right
well because I'm going on this date after
it's with a boy who I haven't seen in a couple months
oh okay
so we like used to date and we've been on and off
uh huh and I just wanted to come and see him again
but look like my best ever
and we just wanted to look really good for my date tonight
I think you can make it you think so
hahaha
after makeover yeah
yeah you get more confidence
you know exactly yes
exactly exactly
I'm pretty sure that you can make it today hahaha
by end of the day hahaha
and is he gonna be here or oh
he's here he's coming here
he's gonna come in 4:30 4:30 yeah
you can get it done by 4:30 OK OK
you're the one for me hello
hahaha
and I know
thanks mate thank you today
do you want to send some hairstyle
I just like wanted it to be like oh wavy yeah
wavy style yeah yeah
just like really like pretty wow
like Flippy Flippy yeah okay
I recommend this some hairstyle okay
which one do you like hmm
I think that's really pretty wow
I think they are
I have good good idea because of your look is very pretty
mm hmm yeah
yeah um um what over there
Uh, no, no, I'm checking my hair right now.
He said he wanted to wavy his length and met a guy who did it today.
do you have a date yeah
oh and the somnam yeah somnam no boyfriend
somnam no boyfriend yeah he's not boyfriend he's not boyfriend
we used to like date
and then we stopped seeing each other and then I texted him
and I'm seeing him
tonight so I haven't seen him for like two months wow
so you like him you like him
You have to let me fall in love haha
uh do you have this uh reference outfit today uh sure your outfit
for my outfit yeah
yes
today is very important it's a special day yes yeah
I change the pop it to your hair hmm
leave it to me okay yeah
should I use it this one
yes yeah
can you show her please oh yeah
I have everything like I didn't want anything to get wrinkled
so one more wow yeah
wow it's very so pissed cake so tight wow
it's cute so cute
IC AU Audi DI Oh my god oh my god
I can already do it haha Corona I have to do it aww thank you aww
so cute
Haha shall we go for a make up yes make up
haha finally makeup time
Is there a story between you two? Oh, two months ago?
Ah, we kept in touch, but then we lost contact for two months, then ah ah.
I contacted my boyfriend again and decided to have dinner with him, do you know some
do you know some what is a some
how do I how can how do I explain the some how do I
explain the some But this is in English is it like a man and women the
before the cami chemistry between
the two of us yeah it's like
yeah cami cami that's some okay okay is there an English
like there's something before
be a girlfriend boyfriend
yeah yeah just hang out there's like people say situationship ah
situationship
okay yes ship situation situation ship oh I learned a English today
okay ship situation we call it in Korea some okay some it's like
something at the different word some
cause it's like something's going on
something's going on with between us
you know yeah
so funny okay
so when where did you guys meet
on him him
oh I love that one
the is like a dating app right
uh huh
so he lives in New York too
Yeah then why you
why you don't why you guys no contact each other
it's hard it's hard really
cause hmm
you never know people aren't ready to be in relationship right
right
timing is timing is really important
yeah timing is everything actually
you know I know yeah
so this this
this moment is timing uh huh
oh my god
I'm hoping I'm really happy like this special moment you come here
I'm so excited I know because of
because today is the special day
I will not be too glam looks really natural
want to be natural you know
with the natural beauty yes
But now that I see myself as a man, men see me as pretty.
Looks like someone on a date
I think I was trying to associate a lot of these things with you.
If I miss you and feel this way, I can't do it again.
You don't want it to be too visible, so do something in moderation.
I think I got something right.
It definitely looks a bit natural
It's glam and all that. I love my job and my current life.
So that you can feel like a mature woman who is living a good life, etc.
I wanted to save you well
I need to make you love me so much haha
when I apply foundation I mixed up with fixer
it helps oh makeup long lasting
so when you feel dry uh huh fixer like this uh huh
with it dry absorbing and like this oh it's stay really long lasting
oh I love it whoa yes this is crazy
I don't want to put a lot of foundation
I I want lightweight foundation yeah
and don't put it too much
next to the eye primer
not too grand right he he he he
좀 생기 있는 느낌 주고 싶어서 로즈 골드 느낌 좀 넣어서
해 드렸던 거 같아요
cover the redness
in gold you're the one I need the most yeah look at the mirror
wow that's pretty do you see yeah rose gold look actually it's
not old to have to dump yeah that's really pretty it's just old
but they have a good self confidence haha you
could be the rest
when do your boyfriend comes
oh sorry when do you when do you when when is he when he come
he's coming here at 4:30 4:30 yeah yeah very soon
do you feel nervous no no no not yet I will
can you smile it just okay I mean the like you're sad so
just smile okay great great great oh you did it really good
let's do it do it do it yeah
yeah
I love New York City people
아 너무 너무 근데 부러웠어요 왜냐면 그 청춘의 설렘 이런 거
같았어요 너무 보기 너무 좋았고 OK you like them
you like them me too
I still think it's not like too much I think it looks really nice
and hoping that Brian would think the same thing
Wow so pretty oh my god this color is really perfect for you
Wow, it sticks well, it sticks well, right. Um, you're so pretty. Um, it's the best.
you're so beautiful this is your color beautiful
Wow you princess wow
stop
let me throw ah sorry
oh I see it he's coming here he's gonna come at 4:30 4:30 yeah
I'm here to see the Julian us too yeah nice
oh hello
hey stop
Julia's friend yes yes nice to meet you
what's your name Brian Brian yeah yeah nice to meet you ah Miran
LA Miran LA Miran oh that’s good hahaha
oh
uh how long does it take
whoa
he's coming
Brian hahaha
your
face is red so handsome guys
I want to say I saw you here I saw you here I
I saw you here I saw you here
don't turn your face red
oh oh haha oh
falling in love how to do it hahaha
Bro, please hold my head just once. Yes yes let’s do it 1 2 3 4
5 6 7 8 9 10 Yes, I don’t have that, I don’t have that, thank you haha
I also have a Cliff Bar that's just another
protein bar it's better though it's like you're trying to poison
me wait did you want a go bar
I also have a Cliff Bar I'm trying to feel your your body
Brian
would you like to some water and drink and no haha
thank you oh
it's okay yeah
yeah okay
thanks
bungoh bang
bung bung apa Yang Ada oh
so I'm good I
I yeah yeah yeah OK
thank you so much
정혁아 줄리아 옷을 갖다 놨어 저기 있냐고요
200 we can eat this we can eat this yeah I ate one yeah
which one chocolate one
this is like the best level to it you know
I think right now I would make teeth Jack yeah right now
it's like all of my teeth right now
that's so bad oh no that's horrible what can I do go to the bathroom
it's everywhere don't walk in here
it's makeup remover
okay done yes
oh oh
wow that's so pretty rotate the your chair
oh wow the other side wow
do you like it yes I love thank you sure we can talk about anything
yeah shall we go for a change outfit yeah yeah yeah okay let's go oh
I need to get out of this
she will coming right now
so please cover your eyes guys
so cute so cute is she coming is she coming
I wanted to well I'm going on a date tonight so I was nervous
because I didn't know what I would look like in the end
I was just excited to see
um my date's reaction and hoping that he liked it a lot
we can swing open it
open it
I just wanna be with you
I just wanna be your
love
I just wanna be your love
I got long locks now
Very moderately natural but a bit lovely
It makes me feel a bit lively while doing it.
I think I wanted to add a rose gold feel to it.
today when I went in I told him that I wanted
very voluptuous like flippy hair
I still think it's not like too much I think it looks really nice
I love them I love it I think I look really pretty
what does she look like she looks so amazing beautiful
I'm actually with short hair really short hair
and now my gorgeous long locks
I want to know your opinion she looks beautiful oh
hahaha hahaha hahaha hahaha
My child is shy. Goodbye, my friend. Hello, thank you, my child. I’m embarrassed. Everything will be fine.
I think it will go well. It suits me well, but my face is turning red when I blow it.
Ah, but like this
I'll take a look, hi hi, but since he's really walking, I really like the guy.
too
Okay, smiling like this
Ah ah, it's so cute. Grumpy Grumpy haha
had to run through the rain to get here but we finally
made it to dinner and you look so beautiful oh
cheers
Now, a little, a little, it's all sorted out now, yes, yes
It's three o'clock now, three o'clock
The last Elizabeth in the class will come now. Yes, I will.
I have to prepare for that
whoa who are you Elizabeth yes welcome to London
oh my gosh it's beautiful thank you hello Elizabeth hello hi
hi this is your manager
Pong Nia to meet you yeah
you can just call me Rachel
Rachel yes
OK nice to meet you Rachel
so have a seat here oh
thank you yeah
we can take care of a lot of bags
yes thank you so much
so please have a seat
alright fabulous
thank you so please have a seat here
oh lovely
so how are you today I'm good
how are you good
good
yes then
oh my gosh thank you so much
this looks so good yeah
try it why don't you try it okay
this very crispy right
yeah yeah
I love it it's like a chip
yeah just like a chip
but it's healthy it's healthy
that's yeah fantastic
it's actually really good
I was very skeptical just cause it's seaweed
yes no
this is really good seaweed is really good for your skin
do you know that no
seaweed is really good for your blood and
you know skin really get cleanse
I can definitely do this okay
so how do feeling about you know
your makeover thing I'm excited
you're excited yeah
I was very interested in the whole um
Korean beauty I heard about the whole pop up situation
and so I'm very interested in the Korean beauty salon
beauty salon yes
hi I'm Elizabeth I am 28 years old
acting and while I do that
I'm a server in multiple jobs in a restaurant
what brought me here was
there was a chance to do like makeover and K Beauty
alright excited to see what this is gonna be
do you have any certain look or picture you want to try
yeah so
I hopefully I can pull this off
but this is kind of the look oh
can I say that if it's too much
no it's not cool though yeah
cause I I've always wanted to do like the the Siren Eye
I usually don't do this type of makeup
but since I was given the opportunity to do something
why don't we go big or go home and yeah we definitely went big
no we can do that okay
okay yeah
and it kind of matches your face
it's all yours it's like wow
a new me a new me yeah
that's it
okay awesome
so I think we are done with the consultation with the consultation
oh wonderful
so just leave it there we can oh
leave it here yeah
I can't finish it uh
when was your last time shampoo your uh
this morning so you don't need shampoo
I mean if you want to
you totally can I heard that they massage oh
you love you have you wanna do it or if it's a possibility or yeah
I mean if that's out of the
it's all possible it's all possible
you're the last customer here
oh really
yes so you can do whatever you want yes
let's do it then so we have a lot of time
okay so we are going to shampoo first okay
let's get started Yay
okay we're just water and vegetables
like seaweed I know
okay fine
I'll leave it um
do you want more like a green tea or just water
the green tea was lovely green tea okay one more green tea
uh huh
okay fabulous
I'll bring my phone
hi Elizabeth
hi I'm Daniel
I'm Elizabeth nice to meet you nice to meet you
I heard that you're an actress
I am oh
are you an actor yes
I am oh really yeah
are you in anything I know
I don't know have you seen Trigga
is that like a K drama yeah
oh OK
OK I'll
I'll write a list I'll be like oh
the the movie called I Hate Korea
it's called I hate Korea yeah
no I haven't
I haven't seen that one did you like being in that movie
was it good oh yeah
yeah it was fun
hey Elizabeth
yes I'll give you a little head massage
oh yes please
okay so just let me know if it hurts okay
is the pressure OK for you
uh huh OK
can I take off your eye cover
uh huh
oh wow
that's bright how was it
oh that's amazing
was it yes
thank you that was in heaven
good job hahaha
this is great
you going for a work today
no I'm off today and I'll watch your show
or your movie haha
but what is it hate Korea
which is horrible what is it
I can't say it I know there's camera in it
yeah that's right
I'm sorry I love Korea
yeah exactly
me too what did you say
you hate Korea no
no no
it's a show it's a show
or a movie actually my bad
I promise I love Korea hahaha
what do you do these days
from like actress thing
I oh man
I do a lot you do a lot
yes so acting's on the side
yeah um
and I serve in like three different ways
three different ways mm hmm
okay so I work at a restaurant and then I also work at
for catering it's like fine dining
which is super fun I also am a barista at a building in Manhattan
what about you me yeah
are you just full time actor
yeah but well
five years ago I did four jobs
four jobs yeah
maybe I did barista
bartender barista and serving stuff
oh you get it
so which one was your favorite survival job
barista bartender
uh I did hairstylist
I did barista about 12 years
oh my goodness yeah
so you can do the latte art
ah of course
I'm terrible maybe just love
love the heart oh really
haha
maybe just that one hey
it is it's hard to do
I forgot how to do it
and I used to work at um do you do retail screen golf
you know screen golf
I know that's screen golf yeah
it is just in Korea I think oh
is it golfing yeah
golfing just in the inside oh
oh nice
how fun cause you know it is hard to earn money
yeah
being an actor yeah
or actress is same same thing
oh yeah
oh yeah is it hard to get audition
it is it is
there are a lot of people
it is a hard industry for sure
but you've been in some some shows me yeah
so that's pretty good I did some yeah
just keep going just keep going
you should keep going yes
I'm telling myself telling you keep going yeah
hard to keep going
I'm trying
I wanna try Hollywood movie one day
you should
you really should
today do you want to up up hairstyle
up to hairstyle yeah
ah yeah
trying something new okay
hahaha
I saw Miss Q today hairstyle
I heard do you want to this you how fun yes
up to and then it's a little bit some pulling down
uh huh and right yeah
do you want yeah
let's do it yes
I like it don't worry
I don't worry
I'm not worried
that's what she always say
don't worry don't worry
trust me yeah yeah
should we go to makeup room
oh yes thank you
hey hi
I'm a pony yeah pony yeah
I'm a makeup artist for you today nice
to meet you yes
uh before the start of doing a makeup OK
when I look at the skin analysis right
you need to put some wrinkle care
I think mm hmm
this is really amazing device
yeah it's very new
oh wow
yes OK
so are they gonna show like a picture
yes you'll see it's a real time result alright
let's go for it
okay so you have a combination skin okay
and you have a very dehydrated
I really like it's intense in bottle
you can see that right
yes you have very dry skin
yes yes
so you need more hydration
oh I agree
yeah absolutely it's parched
so I'm gonna use this product
yeah this is for good
the lifting yeah
don't forget to use the lifting cream every day
it's very important okay
yeah understood
yes
especially this part ah
can you feel this the texture
oh yeah
so you can use this uh
put on makeup mm hmm yeah
underneath makeup yeah
with no problem oh beautiful
yes
I mean it feels amazing on my skin haha
feel very good yes
Yeah I can see the glow yeah
oh you can see your skin is haha yeah
glowing right now oh my God
the glow part is so pretty
oh okay cool yes
and then
uh I heard you have already the reference the photo yeah
can I see that absolutely yes
so nervous okay
oh
the Dark Siren
this part is so good oh
thank you and then yeah
I love the lip color Dark Siren
yes yeah
I love this mood too yeah yes
Wow Siren What comes to mind when you think of Siren?
Cold and captivating
It has a strong feeling of a water-breathing fairy, but there's also a dark character in front of it.
So, what I was thinking was just something with a slightly decadent feel.
I put a lot of effort into making it sexy without making it stuffy.
but yeah this time is totally trying a little yeah OK
the skin makeup hmm
look at this that's really nice look at this yeah
if you need a more food coverage we can use two layers
yeah so it was first layer yeah second layer oh nice
and then use color corrector to look up
I look awake oh
I look just super awake yes
you like it wow
hmm any plan uh after this makeup
what no I don't have any plans
no you have to make yeah I know something I have to make
something I really do
maybe
yeah maybe calling to your friend or
yeah have some dinner alone yeah it would be romantic yeah yeah yeah
why not yeah of course
and take a selfie with myself absolutely ha ha
oh I just I can't go home looking like this yes are you kidding me
what what if I go to the grocery store will that work grocery store
yeah yeah it's gonna be good a serving
that's great don't forget to take a selfie even if you are alone
yes
I'll take a selfie right in the cereal aisle
I'm gonna have a what what's that
what's that
yes yes
그러면은 우리 레오 씨가 여기서 좀 언제 갈까요 네
I'm not nervous oh my gosh
I'm like a renowned make up artist to have to do this is
the first time I've done
it I'm so honored to be here no hahaha
나오셨습니까 꼭 얘기해 주세요 나 봐야 돼서 아 나오셨습니다
oh my God it's so pretty so pretty
oh my God I love it you look so pretty thank you so pretty
you guys nailed it oh my God thank you
yeah she really wanted it you look great thank you ready
oh my God good thing OK bye
oh my God beautiful oh I love it oh you're gonna be changed like her
yeah so a little opposite though yeah
but you have to take a selfie a lot okay yes yeah
I will do that just for you yeah
the No. 1 makeup artist in Korea hahaha
oh my God the swimming I know it's so great I love it okay sorry
yeah it's okay it's okay
pony my makeup artist she knew what she was doing um
she just had the picture had the vision
went for it and she really knew her makeup work
It's okay for me to go like this now, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay. Come in and check.
When I did it, my sister did my makeup.
That's why I keep thinking that I should upload more because
Sam's makeup is really good.
Should I give the bangs a little highlight? Yes.
Well, okay, okay, just stay here just a little longer.
I think it would be nice to do it this far, huh.
Like this
You can ask questions and receive feedback right away
There's really no chance. If you look in the mirror now, look at those eyes.
I was happy to draw the bed here, but it would be better to leave it here a little longer.
I don't think the balance will be good. I like the area around the eyes.
You really inspired me a lot
While I'm at it, I'm going to set up some recipes and I'm going to use this.
Look down please look down oh down yeah yes
oh really that was a proper tutorial
wow it's pretty yeah
wow ah smokey wow it's amazing it's crazy wow
I think it's okay. Wow, if you come in, say to me, ah, Lavet Yadis, they're cool. Wow.
Hey nice feeling
There really is so how long have you lived in New York um four years
four years uh huh so where do you come from I'm from Colorado Colorado
Colorado Colorado wow Colorado wow yeah and
I know
yes this is do you know song song I don't know yes and
oh you didn't no
I I middle school
hmm it's a long time ago I middle school that time I learned
song it's name is Colorado of Spring
Colorado spring yeah do you know yeah Colorado
yeah the back of my mind
do you know it's a very traditional song
there's a song is that a Korean song no no Coloria is a
traditional Korean Colorado song
yeah really I didn't know that really
it's because of my sound it's very bad
no no
that's not good it's not good it's in
and then real it's Colorado song real
no you say lovely
she's disappointed
Araralala lalala, check the child, yes.
Okay mom, this detergent has color.
When I was in middle school, we sang at school that it was spring in Colorado.
If you learned that song, can you tell me what it is called in America in English?
It's not like this song, um bro
What are you looking for? On a moonlit night in Colorado On a moonlit night in Colorado Oh, Colorado
속을 찾고 계셨어요 맞아
it's it's really pretty it's really pretty
yes this this this is song oh my gosh
do you have it do you have a can you hear that
what is he doing that's that it is a moonlight on the Colorado
oh my gosh neighbor I have not heard that
that that is a that is a beautiful song yes you really pretty song
yes I do appreciate it that time is many time I wondering is Colorado
I did not know that there was a Colorado Springs song
I heard and it's Colorado nature is very beautiful
oh yeah it's
stunning but this is something it's a story is the mountains beautiful
it's a nice sunrise star moon
it's this is story oh that's so beautiful
yes so beautiful song I like it this is song I know it's so cute
the song yeah umm it's a very well known song to you Narum
oh my God do you like this to hear I do
it's really cool
you ready let's go
let's go
wow I love the show
show good to
you know ya come on Alicia Bell
hi I'm Elizabeth
what brought me here was to do like makeover and Kate Beauty
I've always wanted to do like the
the Siren Eye dark Siren yes
yeah I love this mood too
yeah yes
alright excited to see what this is gonna be
come on Ellie's the best oh my God
Wooo
yeah
oh my god
thank you thank you
This is definitely out of my comfort zone
I usually don't do this type of makeup
it's like smoky cat eye situation
looked like a badass me my lips look huge
yes yeah
I drove yeah
wow
do you like this hairstyle
yes I do wow
so nice I like it because it has like texture to it so I was impressed
thank you thank you
Yeah I was
I was really excited it was like a whole
it was a whole new look I mean at first I was like
oh wow I have to get used to this
that would just be silly to just go straight home
uh
Goodbye
Hey, look, I'll give you a statute of limitations for dismantling. A statute of limitations for dismantling.
Disband, thank you for your hard work, you worked hard today as well. Decoration, decoration, flower decoration.
Now, Quickly, Quickly, please organize it haha Okay, let’s start organizing it now.
That's what it's like to put it on. This is how our emotions intersect.
I am the sunshine pouring down the sidewalk
Hello, yes, it feels like some kind of holiday today.
Haha, it looks like my mom's back during the holidays. I got this today.
I brought it. What is this? It's a very pretty camera.
civil affairs
Mr. came down, yes, good morning, good morning, good morning. Be pretty. Be chic today, yes, yes.
Go slowly
Yes, let's go. Should I take a picture with my digital camera today? Oh, okay, wait a minute. I need to take a picture like this.
I think it's because I filmed it from the bottom up.
It's not a wide angle so uh we did it like this
There has to be
two three one two three
He takes good pictures, he takes good pictures, he’s a good expert. No matter what they say, he’s good, he’s a real expert.
Even if I became a producer
Whatever you say, did you do well? It could be in the fashion field.
Hahahaha, relax a little. Oh, I’m sorry. I have asthma.
have got
It was a failure earlier, teacher.
It's okay. I have a sore throat. I'll do my best to provide you with water today as well.
Ah
I think I was here, but I went over there and said, Oh, I'm happy, I'm happy
Customers waiting for five minutes in the store
Please write down. No, I memorized this, but I can't remember it. Let's take a test.
No, sleep, test, test, ah, how much should I cut?
Do you want to
Ah, just cut two more at a time. Oh, really, but the one in front is also correct.
No, that's right, I'm glad
When was the last time I cut my hair? It was yesterday. This haircut is safe for me.
It's really dangerous.
Are you okay with the road? Do you like this Land? Uh-huh, uh-huh, how is this?
This is the teacher's note, the English note. You worked really hard, so yeah, me too.
I studied like this
I'm just more nervous about the woman I know. I thought I should use this expression better, but I didn't.
It doesn't make sense. It's something you have to get used to, but what about that one?
Do you have any travel plans recently? Do I have travel plans?
do you have any plans
travel plan do you have any
recently
hahaha
recently recently
recently it's recently
recently but recently
The pronunciation is really different.
recently recently is this man art is disney recently
any coming up do you have any travel coming up
do you have any travel plans coming up coming
up I don't know
Now let's go in
Now, you have to do it quickly, it's Kickle, it's Kickle, quickly, Kickle
I don't think
I'm getting used to this now, so I'll have to look at it. Oppa, I'll do that today.
Finding a walkie-talkie is so easy in the morning, but it’s easy for me.
I'm going to become one with BC now.
I think you're here
hi hi there
welcome to Danza thank you so much
nice to meet you it's so cute in here it's cute here Walter
yes Walter and this is Ethan hello Ethan hello Ethan I'm Daniel
nice to meet you nice to meet you
hi there
nice to meet you I'm Walter thank you hi there Walter
Walter nice to meet you hi please have a seat here yes cool
so we have like a work of menu so sweet thank you
do you wanna do this looks good or yeah this
one I wanna try that yeah great choice
yeah I would try this yeah do this
yeah thank you thank you
hi my name is Walter Higginbottom I'm 23 years old um
I live in Brooklyn New York I'm from Raleigh North Carolina I studied
musical theater I got my degree in musical theater
and so I came up to New York City attempting to become an actor
in musical theater
hi there nice to meet you OK
so Walter um
Walter um
are you ready for the consultation
yeah let's do this
yes OK
please follow me do you want him to come with me
yes alright
we have the same brain when it comes to like picking things up
I swear every single time
that goes well with this
yeah do you like it
yeah it's delicious
yeah that is so good
so let's move on to makeover thing
let's do it yes yup
so um
water um
can I ask you what brings you here for your totally makeup
yeah absolutely
so I kind of during the day
I feel like I'm kind of in more like a preppy nerdy look
yeah maybe something a little bit more um
intense than what I typically go for
it's a little bit more like grungy grungy
yeah okay
so I was fun yep yep yes
OK so
tonight me and my roommates are hosting a rooftop party
it's something we do every once in a while
it'll be really lovely
and I wanted to look do like an edgy look for tonight
I'm gonna hopefully surprise them with how different I look uh
it'll be a lot of fun
for yeah
I don't have any like references or anything
you can just like go for it
you're open to everything
I'm open to anything yeah
OK I'm not closed off to anything
you're just a great customer
thank you they're just expert and magician
so you can just trust them
I'll take care of this something
so yeah just leave it there and you're gonna uh
you're gonna sit waiting for that right
OK just you can do this yeah
leave it yeah
just leave it there am I following you
oh yeah
should I take mine out of
oh yes
that would be great thank you thank you so much
gonna see
it how's this thing
it's so good is it I ate it so fast
nice to meet you nice to meet you
what was your name yeah
my name is Chahong I'm Walter
Nice to meet you Walter
and today you're a hairstylist too
perfect yes
nice to meet you nice to meet you
I have a lot but yeah I can't tell
This is curly. The curls are getting very severe.
It starts with the three type. It's exactly the one three-bi three-bi type. Yes.
I think I need to cheer up. This really doesn't go away. It's a little harder than I thought.
It will take some time.
Oh, it takes a lot of strength, my wrist is okay, it’s okay, oh here.
Color Is Berry Beautiful Thank You Beauty Is Berry Softy
I apply the coconut oil coconut oil yes now perfect it perfect yes
have you uh
tried this and straightened hair before I
have I actually did a show in college
a musical in college where I played like a rock
star type character and my hair was very straight
wow it was very long oh
I had my hair straightened once before in college
I did a show and then I did it myself and it was
did not look good it was pretty a pretty messy
I know like some like rock or punk or edgy looks
it's mostly people with straight hair
but I was worried that straight hair wouldn't look right
I have so much hair yes
really so much wow haha
why is it long sudden
I know suddeny long
no I can't do that
no no this is not done
trust her no
I'm trusting the process yes
she's just No. 1 hairdresser in Korea
that's so cool yes
so famous hairdresser wow
are you using those straightener
go for it yes
this is only boom
a coconut always sound yeah
don't worry not me
sometimes I can't deny so depressed
so depressed so cool
so cool
wow so handsome
thank you so beautiful
very different so gorgeous
thank you so
so is so is OK
wow so sexy
all of the beauty wow
every adjective wow
so nice
it's some add some volume
wow
Ah Yepuda
It suits you very well
I'm so shocked
it's so it looks so cool it's so different wow yeah
I wish they could have done this for my show it looks a
bit much better
When everything in the world doesn't go your way
It suits you very well. It's very nice.
Well done, very good. This is Korean style yes very cute
Korean student Korean student style
so cute thank you
thank you so much fun
follow me
change your room
thank you thank you so much yeah
thank you so much
Then, can you finish it quickly in 15 minutes?
uh
Haha, hey, I need to do my hair too, so if you're going to give it to me
Give it to me neatly haha I have to get my hair sticky again
Well, then, really, yes, I won’t finish it, I won’t, I won’t, because you didn’t do it.
new room new room have a good time thank you wow so many things yes
so cute yeah so pretty
so many things yes it's called just glitter
so cute right so cute so so cute this is cute
it's so cute in America it's just so like yes boring
oh look at this oh my God wait jelly bean so cute right yes
okay let's see I thought uh you are very sweet uh as well with the
grunge you broke yeah how about
um and I would love to do something like a little bit more intense
like a something a bit sharper like stronger sharper ah yeah
how about this look is this too dark no that's cool yeah
I love this contour yeah I like the highlight on the nose
oh OK I trust you
No, really
He’s handsome, he’s so handsome, those glasses and everything.
I wonder if it's too hidden in my curly hair.
The more I decorate, the more handsome I am.
I think I was just saying this with strong feelings a while ago. Okay, let’s start.
any plan after this makeup um yeah we were gonna
maybe do like a party tonight
but I think that a party and on the rooftop
but wow since everyone likes
graduated with their degree in musical theater
that I'm really close with um
in college so everyone moved up here like right after we graduated
and so we have like a lot of friends up here
me and my roommates oh really
mm hmm that'll be fun
me and Ethan went to the same school
oh mm hmm
same degree and everything
how we became friends
he is my very best friend in the world
we studied musical theater at the same school
and he just graduated this may
whereas I graduated last may
and he actually moved to New York like two weeks ago
and I'm so excited to be reunited with him
can I see that uh your nail
oh yeah of course
yeah oh
hahaha
so funny thank you
haha
thank you so much hi
thank you
I heard I heard you are uh
work with drag queen oh yes
that's what I wanna do yeah yeah
ah you wanna do
I want to get into that yeah
ah
I really like drag show in Korea
you know I have a lot of drag friends in Korea
really have oh my gosh
that's amazing yeah
I also yeah
I also collaborate with many drag Queens of course
and with makeup yeah
that was so amazing I really love drag
drag art yeah
me too I I love it
I would love to be able to do that one day
yeah can I see a picture of the drag queen
yes I can
oh my God so excited
yeah let me see if I can find one
what's your name uh Ethan
Ethan I'm Leo
Leo yeah
OK nice to meet you
but yeah like it's been
I would love to be able to do that one day
oh lovely
yeah oh yes
I love the outfit too thank you
yeah like
what was the theme this was for Halloween oh my God
did you done your makeup by yourself
yeah you good
thank you yes
the colour yeah
wow you good
thank you what is it
I don't even know
I was just experimenting with like different colors and stuff
yes the pose
hahaha nailed it
but yeah one day I want to make up in New York for a drag queen
yeah no
that would be amazing yeah
before makeup I want to go to show show yeah
first time yeah
yeah that's so cool
yeah thank you
nice meeting you okay
meeting you too yeah thank you
OK
yeah
oh
Hello, yes, Abby can’t come.
I think it's time to be my friend
On uh, should I get a friend who does drag? Then I'll change it to Aiden.
Jeonghyeok
Yes, I don’t think Abby Son will be able to come next time.
Eden now instead
I think I'll do it. Ah, my friend. It's an urgent package.
I don't think Abby will be able to come next, so the four of them
I think my friend will do it, really.
so Ethan I I have a question yeah I was just wondering
if your you know since your friends is yeah changing a lot
yeah what about you doing me
I'm sure yeah I would I would I would love to
yeah do you love to do it yeah I'm down yeah sure sure
OK so let's OK sure conversation OK
so since you're the surprise guest here we are yeah
Lego, the third person is insulting, so this person's friend is going to be fun.
so have a seat here
the best shampoo guy
yeah awesome hey hi Daniel Ethan nice to meet you Ethan
can I get your glasses oh yes yeah thank you thanks
Ah, this friend also knows what a friend is
Wouldn't it be really fun to keep it a little secret?
Please tell the secret to others
don't mention it a bit
please follow me to the makeup room
do you need any more water or anything um
can I have a I don't know I'll do a water yeah
you do water yeah we have a lot of things but
I actually I'll do another the banana
the banana milk latte yeah latte can I yes thank you
yes thank you I can recognize him by his voice
oh my god
hi
hi hey Ethan nice to yes Ethan yeah
so what do you want today I was thinking
maybe like a cool like graphic liner look graphic liners yeah
I already did one oh yeah let me show you one
wow
I have a graphic look a lot of
I really like this makeup, just
The line is usually straight like this, but there are branches extending from this line.
That's how I put on my makeup. I feel like I'm a little out of it these days.
oh yes yeah exactly is that you want that's like
yeah that's what I was thinking like something cool like yes something
cool like a like the fun life yeah
that's awesome and which color
would you prefer oh I mean maybe blue to like match the shirt maybe
yeah like maybe dark blue yeah dark blue
okay let’s do it with
before we color makeup we should use the white color concealer first
let's do the black liner let's draw wings first
yeah
that's exactly what I was thinking
like something like that yeah yeah like the graphic
let's mascara first mm hmm
usually mascara before um actually I usually I do it last usually
you go OK haha very great
I was surprised too. Did I stab myself? Did I get something in my eye?
Or, I was wondering if this product was too strong.
I just wonder what makes you
get here yeah it's always like that oh
yeah it's not you like it even when I do it myself it happens
Yeah OK OK
he he sorry okay just tear it down he he
oh it's okay I'm sorry the last thing
great gosh they're falling they're falling yeah it's okay it's okay
It's become a habit to not show that I'm nervous.
I think it's because I'm too nervous in front of the person getting my makeup done.
It looks unprofessional, so rather than just shaking the brush.
I just put it down more slowly and looked around even more slowly.
While doing this
I'm thinking, what should I do? What should I do? What should I do? Why are you doing this?
I think we need a waterproof eye makeup OK right
this is dusty blue shadow
I love it man I love it I love it
crying it's so embarrassing
very much teary but we're gonna get there we're gonna get there yeah
okay oh it was fun
okay uh now I'm gonna use the foundation
you have a little bit pale
pink yes so I think it's too bright a little bit
are you mixing it yes smart
for your one and only color my unique shade unique yes
Tada boom yeah I think it's so yeah good match so yeah good match
Iron Fist with a twist we like honey
오늘 루프탑 파티 가신대요 루프탑 파리 으흠
how many oh gosh last one was like 40 people I know
and my friend is having a going away party it's gonna be like
probably even more I make it though wow sounds fun
오케이 멋있죠 너무 잘 어울릴 것 같아요 멋있지 않아요 어 요거 갑니까 네
재밌을 것 같아요
discourage with my reality
then I hear my faith keep on telling me yeah yeah
I look down
and hold
it down I will never fall too hard to wear this crown just remember
cause I don't love anymore
and then we use the eyeshadow on your lips
oh really
mm hmm with the eyeshadow brush
then using this
this color
and then
I'm using this eyeshadow the center of your lips
more grungy punky
standing tall when the man says no
oh yeah
very tall yes cute
wow look at you
so different oh
my God so different skin
rock star rock star
uh huh
wow it's so much better
so curled wow
so cool so cool what I thought
Wow, it’s really changed. Wow, so different ear line.
Come on, Walter is coming. It's Walter After.
hi my name is Walter Higgins
bottom normally I'm kind of more preppy and a little bit more nerdy
with my glasses and toes
and stuff like that I wanted to try to do something
cool but I didn't feel like I could really hit the Mark
wow
wow oh my gosh wow wow
oh my gosh so cool
wow so cool
shake shake shake oh my God that's so cool take take take
oh that's so cool
It went so well, my hair too
I think it went really well and the makeup turned out exactly as Doyoon wanted. Yes.
But I had a lot of fun with it
That friend wanted to become a rock star, so I made him a rock star.
At first I was a student studying, but now I'm just a student
I felt like I couldn't go home, but it's okay once in a while, right?
where do you want um I trust your instinct
It's so soft and has real force. There aren't any pores.
No, the machine is handsome. It's really the type that gets more handsome the more you decorate it.
Oh this is so good
Let's try this. With this in mind, we decided to decide on Lubu.
k beauty is versatile
everything was lovely it exceeded my expectations
oh my gosh oh shit on yeah good
haha yeah oh your hair thank you guys so good oh my God
oh so nice
thank you guys so much different man
different yeah I feel so confident yeah
feeling like a rock star yeah
wow so good very different
so good an outfit love thank you guys so much
and then you have to wait for your
oh is he doing something yeah of course he is
thank you so much that was that was crazy
how is it going
ah
what are you doing I'm loving it my eyes are always really watery no
it looks amazing
Oh my god oh my god bling bling kid what
What did you do? What on earth did you do with WoW art?
You did that, it's pretty, uh uh
I'm excited to see Walter too hahaha
oh the ripple I love it
Oh my
I never thought I would try this at a real shop.
I like it so much, it’s so amazing, yes OK we’re coming
he's coming I think I'm ready
close your eyes covering your eyes
open open haha
I was not expecting to be made over at all today like I was fully
expecting to just be here and support Walter yeah I was really really
excited but I was not expecting it at all but yeah
oh
my God
look at those girls have you seen those girls I just wanna
hey I cannot you look you look incredible oh wait
hold on oh
we need to start a band like we do need to start a band rock band
start a rock band hey
wow your makeup is gorgeous
wait I need to actually see oh
you can't see okay is your hair straightened
yes it's straightened wait oh
it's yeah yeah
yeah gorgeous
Gorgeous the lashes I know the lashes right
love it but your makeup is so pretty thanks I love that who did it
me you yeah
that's so good thank you love this is so fun I had so much fun yeah
thank you for having us like my life has changed like this is like
Seriously like this is so much fun like K beauty era yeah
seriously we're gonna get into it
thank you so much nice to meet you nice to meet you I'm gonna go
oh
You see, it's lunchtime. Yes, food has arrived. Meal.
I'm here, shrimp, double, double, double, shrimp, shrimp, here's the roll.
I think there's shrimp and all the food is delicious.
It's not because I'm hungry. I ate a banana. I ate a banana, but it's still good. Hmm.
hi I'm a makeup artist for you today I'm Riley nice to meet you yes
let's see her yeah
okay
so lovely your eye color thank you how can I call this color
we call it turtle turtle shell
ah I didn't know that turtle shell yeah wow it's a so interesting
hahaha yeah I just wonder
hello nice to meet you
hello
nice to meet you I'm Riley
wow
you're so pretty you're
so
pretty
here is some gold jewelry
gold jewelry it's a little too yellow right
it's a little too yellow right
how do you think it looks like
ah right
Choose a color for that person About yourself
You know me well. Oh, it was really difficult.
I'm a second year resident in neurology yeah that's amazing
seeing her in a lot of pain
and then I became a brain doctor because
I want to help people like her the doctors that took care of her
The word mother itself
It's heartbreaking to give, but the thought of his mother is so beautiful.
it's a mother thing you cannot turn it off love you Mama
I love you so
much I love you so much I love
you
so
much I love you so much